Yair Charit

+972-54-440-8838 yaircharit@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/yair-charit in yaircharit.github.io 🚩

Summery:

B.Sc. in Computer Science Graduate from Tel-Hai College, Israel. I am a quick and strategic thinker and problem solver. Great working as part of a team as well as leading it when necessary. Experienced working and communicating online.

Experience:

3. 2019 – present: Assembly and OS Instructor at "Magshimim", Cyber Education Center. Teaching and managing a class, delivering complex ideas in limited time (currently online) **2020-present:** freelancer fullstack developer: web design, custom automations, dynamic pages, database set-up and interface, etc.

Technologies:

Operating Systems: Windows, Linux.

Programming Languages: C, C++, C#, Java, Assembly, MATLAB, Bash, HTML, CSS,

Git, Git bash, Python, JavaScript, SQL. (Hands-on courses avg: 92)

Basic knowledge in: Photoshop, IT.

Education:



2018 – Present: (B.Sc.) Computer Science - Tel-Hai college, Israel.

- Outstanding performance in all programming focus courses.
- Deep understanding of OOP coding and computer's fundamentals (low and high level programming languages).



2012–2016: Highschool education- "Hamoshava", Zichron Ya'aqov.

- 5 units in Computer Science and English
- Excelled in Computer Science.

Qualifications:



2018: English for Work – The Language Gallery, London

Languages:

Fluent in Hebrew and English.